### Priya Pathak 3D Artist

jimmiedebrooke@mail.com 832-205-4645 jimmiedeportfolio.com

# **Summary of Qualifications**

Passionate 3D artist with over 5 years of experience in 3D modeling, rigging, and animation. At CreativeMonk Games designed and defined 20 immersive game settings using 3ds Max tools and ensured project integration on a daily basis. The father of the "Professor R." animated character, responsible for the character rigging and pre-effects processing in Maya.

# **Work Experience**

#### 3D Artist

CreativeMonk Games July 2016–July 2018

- Created high-quality 3D models of 20 game settings in Revit.
- Defined detailed environments with the use of 3ds Max toolset.
- Worked on produced content scaling.
- Textured assets for rendering and optimized Shader.
- Cooperated closely with other artists to obtain the best final results.

## **Key achievement:**

Nominated to "Digital Art Awards 2018" for creating unique winter environments.

#### 3D Animator

CreativeMonk Inc.

Jan 2013-Jun 2016

- Designed the main character of the "Professor R." animated movie.
- Created over 500 character models in line with the character effects team requirements.
- Manipulated the character to interact with digital environment using Maya.
- Closely cooperated with the editorial team to ensure character integrity.

#### **Key achievement:**

 Nominated for "Animated Characters Jury Awards 2016" for creating Professor R. character

### Education

#### **BA, Computer Animation**

Ringling College of Art and Design, Sarasota, FL 2012–2015

## **Visual Arts Program Grad**

Douglas Anderson School of the Arts, Jacksonville, FL 2011-2015

# **Key Skills**

- Adobe: Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign, After Effects
- 3D Software: Maya, Revit, 3D Studio Max
- Character Modeling
- Rigging
- Animation
- Collaboration
- Open-Mindedness
- Project Management
- Organization

# **Specialization**

- Rigging: creating skeletons for a variety of 3D models using Maya and 3D Studio Max tools; performed character and object weight controls and painting, added inverse kinematics to 3D models; ensure achieving realistic character and object motion.
- **Animation:** controlled rigged characters in real time; applied motion capturing techniques to rigs; worked with control curves and constraints to manipulate characters and objects.